At ease, I'd like to welcome the newest no limit soldier
Mr. Snoop D O double G and he brings to the tank
Money, power, respect, leadership
Street knowledge and wisdom

D.P.G., yah D.P.G.
Pop the Champagne
Once you break this of you can't get twisted
So pay attention and listen

Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free
Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free

Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free
Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free

Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free
Welcome to my world nigga and it's V.I.P
And the bitches and the Bud for free

Welcome to this world that you never thought existed
And you got to be a soldier to be enlisted
Listen, I'm gonna take your mind and your body and your soul
On a whole li'l trip, just don't lose your grip

Wait a second, where is the sack?
You don't have to ask no questions just jump in the back
And leave your strap, 'cuz there ain't none of that
Where we goin'? It ain't nuthin' but 808, beats and flauntin'

Niggas showin' niggas love, hoes suckin' dicks
That's how we do it, 'cuz everything is in the mix
Doggy Land, Doggy World, Snoop World whatever
It don't matter 'cuz we 'bout it and homies down to do whatever

Everything is legit, and the bitches the shit
And niggas they give you love 'cuz dey down for it
Now that's just how it goes and all the hoes on me
And everything is V.I.P and that's on D.P.G.

...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
Featuring mia x

Slow down cause i can't take the heat slow down
(slow down baby slow down baby)
It's wicked in these streets
Slow down cause i can't take the heat slow down
(ohhhhhhhhh slow down)
It's wicked in these streets

Snoop:
Life ain't nothing but a big old twist
A lot of times when i'm smoking
I'm doing that just to reminisce
It's funny on how shit be
A lot of money, make y'all wanna come get me
But look here, i work hard for all the things i got
And to hang with a nigga's just an intricate plot
You smoke my weed, you try to bang my hoes
And talk bad about a nigga, behind closed doors
But look here dog, a hoe once told me loc
Bite the hand that feeds you, and you'll wind up broke
Bitch niggas don't deserve to kick it with rich niggas
Nigga we seven figure niggas
And we bigger than the biggest hip hop niggas in rap
And when we get to spittin' make sure y'all step back
You with that? cause if you ain't clown,
We from the d-o double g, we groupie true, and slow down

Slow down (slow down now) cause i can't take the heat, slow down
(i can't take the heat, i can't take the heat)
It's wicked in these streets
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
f/ Fiend, Mystikal

[Snoop Talking]
Hell yeah
That was a mothafuckin' trip
The way y'all niggaz had the whole world sayin' UH!, na, na, na, na
This here the Doggfather, rappin' on this shit here
Check this out

Chorus:
Let me here ya say
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay (come on, everybody say)
Everybody, let me hear ya say
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay

[Fiend]
I run with convicted felons
Scream, yellin'
Bitch I'ma soldier!
Stick in my chrome reciever, and I fins to get it on
Influenced by the dolja
Blastin' at the rollers
Callin' couple of soldiers
Fuckin' up with this song bitch
Your mom shoulda told ya
I ain't nothin' nice
Snoop brought the boss
I got the spark, lets go on a body high
Put it on my life, and my favorite weed pipe
Soldiers greed, with ice
Watch me budda up in the night
Carefull to forever, the one that? shot him
Bringin' the drama like a punk, but your fucking somebody
Whut Lodi Dodi, send a duce up in dey coupe
But after a hard eight
Snoop and his soldiers gonna make ya say

Chorus:
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay (Jeah, nigga, I can make ya say)
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay (yeah, tank doggs, let me hear ya say)
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay (all my real rap niggaz say)
Woof! mothafucker, Woof! mothafucker
Bow-wow-wow-yippie-yo-yippie-yay (yeah, Mystikal, where you at?)

[Mystikal]
Nigga, all I really wanna do is
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
Get your motherfuckin' glass, 'cus it's a blast from the past
You didn't think we would touch it two times nigga
Gin & juice up in this bitch, yeah
Some of that beats by the pound flavor, you feel me
Get your ice, get your cups, 'cus we about to get fucked up in here
Yeah straight up

I'm still smokin', driftin', swifta than a mothafucka
Twisted off a cup of that 'ole ignat juice
Heated in the seat cup fulla drank
Beatin' up the block in the dark blue tank

Bullet proof vest on my chest for the cause
Diggin' in my draws for dem muthafuckin' laws
Harrassin' a nigga, blastin' a nigga
I ain't seen shit, so why you askin' a nigga

To fucked up off that G-I and juice
C-I get loose, nigga whatchu wanna do
I got a crew but I choose to roll solo
Especially on Sundays dippin' in my low low

[Incomprehensible] spot for the glock
I ain't fuckin' with the hen dogg so toss out the [Incomprehensible]
Put my shit on three wheels for thrills
I hit a corner and make sure my drink don't spill, that's real

Rollin down the street with heat
Drankin', [Incomprehensible] sittin' on D's
Top rolled back so I can feel the breeze
Never slippin', I keep my eyes on my enemies

Rollin down the street with heat
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
[Hook 2X's: Pharrell & Uncle Charlie Wilson]
Ohhh-ohh-oh-ohhh-ohhh... (Oh-hooo!)
Yeahhh, yeahh, yeah, yeahhhh... (Ehh... oh yeah, there's something about
you...)
[Chorus 2X's]
Beautiful, I just want you to know (Oh-hooo!)
You're my favorite girl... (Ehh... oh yeah, there's something about you...)

I know you gon' lose it, this new Snoop shit
Come on baby boo, you gotsta get into it (Oh-hooo!)
Don't fool wit the playa with the cool whip
Yeah-yeah, you know I'm always on that cool shit
Walk to it, do it how you do it
Have a glass, lemme put you in the mood and, (Oh-hooo!)
Lil' cutie lookin' like a student
Long hair, wit'cha big fat booty
Back in the days you was a girl I went to school wit
Had to tell your moms and sister to cool it (Oh-hooo!)
The girl wanna do it, I just might do it
Here to walk wit some pimp-pimp clue wit'
Mommy don't worry, I won't abuse it
Hurry up and finish so we can watch "Clueless" (Oh-hooo!)
I laugh at these niggas when they ask who do this
But everybody know who girl that you is

...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
[Snoop Talking]
Yo whats up P
Yeah man these niggas think that I done fell off man
Think my shit done got weak I guess
Shit nigga I been hustlin' grindin' like a motherfucka
I aint went nowhere knowwhatImean?
Shit guess I got to let these niggas know who I am
What I stand for and what I'm about huh
You feel me check this out BITCH!

[Chorus]
whats my motherfucking name
Snoop Dogg
What I like to do
you like to hustle and ball
x4

[Snoop]
I get up early in the mourning and begin my mission
Brush my teeth then I creeps to the kitchen
Cook some bacon and eggs and put some braids in my head
Stash this pound, put the shit down then I head
To the spot thats hot, fuck a fed
I gotta clock this knot ya heard what I said
Im taking penitentiary chances, dancin with the devil
Im in it to win it for No Limit nigga next level
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
Uh.
Yea.
(Don't Let Go)
Life, life
(Don't Let Go)

I'm the coldest of the coldest, the dopest of the dopest
The smoothest of the smoothest and locest of the locest
The whole world on point for this new joint that I just put together
So kindly, and you can find on the coast with the most lambs
High post, plain coast with a bunch thug niggas, drug dealers
Project fools, C-Murder past dem tools
Shit I'm bout to make these motherfuckers get up
I draw the line between yours and mine
And make sure you don't get lit up
Hit ha on the motha fickin set when dip
Dogg pound mutha Fuckin gangsta crew
Split wigs for a livin everydays thanksgiving
Mutha fuck yall rides, we slides we dippin
Nigga the tanks, driven by the colonel Mr. Master P
Lil Silkky, Mystikal, C and me and Fiend
Nigga don't be trippin, you got my lil homie in the cut
That Soulja Slim nigga, he known for dippin

Wassup 
(Don't let go)
If you love ta bang bang
And the rap game is just like the dope game
The minute you forget it, forget it you finished
Them niggas know when you aint with it
That's when they get ignent 

...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
f/ Mystikal

Mystikal talking
We been holding back to motherfukin long
Nigga fuck the dumb shit
It's time to represent nigga
It's time to represent nigga
It's time to let you niggas now man

Mystikal
I'm the conscious in the toolbox that's coming for the carpenter
I'm the mirror and the comb clipping the scissors that come from the
barber? the godfather
I'm one of the brand new number 2 pencils out the pencil sharpener
I'm the scarlet water out the delta faucet
I'm the rhyming I'm the artist
I'm vomit in the toilet
I'm the comet when it charges
I'm the drama in New Orleans
I'm the vegetables that grow in the garden
All the weeds, dope, and coke at the parties
I'm the M.I.C.H.A.E.L Tyler
I'm the loud blackka, blackka, wakka, wakka coming rom behind yah
I'm the stitches of the shirt that make the polo man trill inside the
Timberland
I'm the bells on trigger man
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
[Hook 2X's: Pharrell & Uncle Charlie Wilson]
Ohhh-ohh-oh-ohhh-ohhh... (Oh-hooo!)
Yeahhh, yeahh, yeah, yeahhhh... (Ehh... oh yeah, there's something about
you...)
[Chorus 2X's]
Beautiful, I just want you to know (Oh-hooo!)
You're my favorite girl... (Ehh... oh yeah, there's something about you...)

I know you gon' lose it, this new Snoop shit
Come on baby boo, you gotsta get into it (Oh-hooo!)
Don't fool wit the playa with the cool whip
Yeah-yeah, you know I'm always on that cool shit
Walk to it, do it how you do it
Have a glass, lemme put you in the mood and, (Oh-hooo!)
Lil' cutie lookin' like a student
Long hair, wit'cha big fat booty
Back in the days you was a girl I went to school wit
Had to tell your moms and sister to cool it (Oh-hooo!)
The girl wanna do it, I just might do it
Here to walk wit some pimp-pimp clue wit'
Mommy don't worry, I won't abuse it
Hurry up and finish so we can watch "Clueless" (Oh-hooo!)
I laugh at these niggas when they ask who do this
But everybody know who girl that you is

...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
Top dollar with the gold flea collar
Dippin' in my blue Impala
(DPG)

Top dollar with the gold flea collar
Dippin' in my blue Impala
(DPG)

Top dollar with the gold flea collar
Dippin' in my blue Impala
(DPG)

Top dollar with the gold flea collar
Dippin' in my blue Impala
(DPG)

It's like 4 and to the 5 and to the 6 and to the 7
I once was told that all Doggs go to Heaven
Well, how ya been? Where ya been and what it look like?
My game trump tight especially when it bump like

Four DPG's gettin' crazy
And No Limit is the label that pays me
Ridin' 'round town layin' game down like Goldie
And I remember what my momma showed me

Told me game recognize game
And stay true to what ya do and don't be ashamed
I got all my game from her sometimes I have to wonder
How I keep from goin' under, I'm a bad muthafucka

I fall to my knees, thank God before I do my thang
I don't know why, I love to gang bang
See life ain't nuthin' but a twist anyway, bitch, anyway
You can say what you wanna say

Just don't get in my way 'cause I'm a mean old
Fiend know, C know and P know, see loc'
We make music for the thugs and the bangers
And the bitches, fuck them R&B singers

She want a nigga with his khackies hangin' real low
In a black rag Sixty-four
Hit it down the street, way clean
Bangin' that real shit nigga like Al Green
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
What's happenin y'all? Big Snoop Dogg

Shootin a shout out to all the lil' rascals out there man

The lil' homies, y'knahmsayin?

Niggaz keep talkin they ain't gon' grow up to be shit

Don't trip, I used to be a lil' rascal too

Look at this lil' rascal now!

Yeah, the lil' rascal done became the Big Snoop Dogg

Follow your dreams lil' homies



Ah check one bopper! Yeah

We goin back, to the hip-hop shop, non-stop baby

A-ha ha ha ha, yeahhh

Where all the deejays use the turntables, like Glocks

A-ha ha ha ha, ahhhhh

We just havin fun, and nobody gets shot!



Now we movin on, to hip-hop and funk

Where Snoop & Bootsy usin music and lyric

To spike yo' punchberry

...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
It's all right
Reflections of the way life used to be
It's all right

Take it back to the Afros and the naturals
Cape cutter picks, we slips into the back holes
O.G., my nigger, for real though
Straight up off that East Side, top of the hill, y'all

I'm lookin' at the overview
Thinkin' 'bout '86, damn, I was overdue
Walkin' in the hood, makin' mix tapes
Tryin' to walk up about the hood
While I'm chucking at the hood

Nigger, talk about the hood that I came from
It raised me real crip crazy, what up, oopsy daisy
Demon or a heathen, schemin' while I'm dreamin'
Screamin' to get even, seein' is believin'
And don't you forget that, get it to you, get back
Hit that kick back, three flies one away

Reminisce about the things that my grand mama use to say
"Stay in your own lane, stay on your own
And quick trying to be grown
Day turn to night and play turn to fight"

It's all right
Yeah, I guess my granny was right
Reflections of the way life used to be
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
[Snoop]
Let cho' mind not be confused
If you can walk this walk nigga take my shoes
New fools, you fools, these fools, all y'all
Talkin bad about me, and my motherfuckin dawg
He ain't trippin, I ain't trippin, but y'all niggaz still dissin
To me, some of these suckers'll never get it
Full clip and if I miss it I'ma tip it on the Crip
And DoggHouse in your mouth, now tell me how you livin
Who the villain, you the villain? Nigga Ren is "The Villain"
My homey from the C-P-T, cold chillin
Now as time flies by I see the game gettin mo' reala
As I get mo' scrilla, can you dig it?
I always tend to come widdit
Gravy train on your brain, nigga come get it
I'm too young to retire, I'm havin fun wit it
See when you learn what to do with it, I'll be done with it
Come with it
[Chorus: KoKane, Snoop]
Go. (just go away). go a-way!
[S] Niggaz can't be trusted
[K] Just come back another day
[S] Niggaz be on bitch shit
[K] Just go far, a-way
[S] Niggaz get it twisted
Just go a-way.
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
[Uncle Chucc:]
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
They say it's? '64 on Vogue's
In the game pain still the same they knocking at your door
Ooo you wanna only talk bad
It's a sad sad thing you dirty low down

Ooo
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
Ooo
I wonder wonder wonder what it do
Wa la la la la la la la la la
Tell me now!
Wa la la la la la la la la la
Wa la la la la la la la la la
Won't you tell me now!
Wa la la la la la la la la la
Snoop Dogg

[Snoop Dogg:]
Independent I'm in it been getting my cash right
Walking through the day time holding my flashlight
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
This is my fuckin' house, this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house
This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house

This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house
This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', fuckin', fuckin', fuckin' house

This is my motherfuckin' house, eh, I'm by the front door
Hear about a blond haired bitch name Cisco
She'll do anythin' for daddy, man, the bitch go
Tell' em what the doormat read, baby, 'Big blow'

Uh, Pyrex and a DIJ scale
Fuck gloves, I got ya all in my fingernails
And I can leave a set of white fingerprints
Chris Tucker, Larenz Tate, Dead Presidents

Dead white boys spread across the coffee table
I don't know, maybe I'll start me up a record label
Fuck it, get high and call what's her name
She like to play this little game call fuck a brain

Lord, when you talk them numbers, sound sophisticated
It ain't nothin' even the Pitbull's affiliated
Yeah and trespassers getting' bust on
G shit even the Coupes got Chucks on

This is my fuckin' house, this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house
This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house

This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', this is my fuckin' house
This is my motherfuckin', this is my motherfuckin'
This is my motherfuckin', fuckin', fuckin', fuckin' house
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
Snoop, Snoopy doo, Snoop doo doo
Fredwreck, Snoop Dogg
Yeah, quit bullshittin' and hit it, man
Hit the shit, man, yeah

If I do, if I don't, if I will, if I won't
I mix the C with the P and live the G with the funk
Got you rappin' at school, my nigger actin' a fool
He got suspended, now he all alone in his room

Playin' my CD, la da dee da dee
East Side shit, Goldilock and big Trey D
On the C, the young homie wanna be me
So I'ma let him, I hope the homeboys don't get him
'Cause they gonna sweat him

Gotta stay on deck for that
If you a buster, you gonna get checked for that
It's so real, homie, don't pop that pill
Dip that now, tell me how does that feel?

I can't stop, gotta go hard in the paint
Can't fake, nigger, put paint where it ain't
Monkey see, monkey do what I say I do
If I take one, you take two

I just wanna let you ride, peer pressure
Get you high, peer pressure
Smoke weed till I die, peer pressure

I just wanna let you ride, peer pressure
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
(I don't need no bitch)
My mama told me never ever trust one, bust one and break 'em
Be 'bout your paper, nigger, take it
Every day's a hustle, got these haters at my neck
Suckers tryna get a check

The Boss Dogg does it, hoes wanna call it what it wasn't
Tryna kiss a nigger all in public, bitch, is you crazy?
I preach pimpin' not pussy
Shit, I heard it all before, I ain't no motherfuckin' rookie
(I don't need no bitch)

I'm a Long Beach, rollin' twenty, playa 'bout his G's
I ain't trippin' off these walls, you know these rats is after cheese
Messin' with my focus, the locust on his grind
Baby, focus on his dick and keep your focus off my time

Stay in the lane that I made for you to chill
Until then it's been real
I gotta handle business and you are nowhere in it
See, trippin' gets you nowhere 'cause bitch, I'm on that

I don't need no bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch all on me
Trippin' and callin' my phone, always lyin'
I don't need no bitch, bitch constantly checkin' on me
Bitch, don't even try it, I'm out here grindin'
That's why I don't need no bitch

We used to rock to the rhythm that didn't stop
Now you tellin' me I need to be gettin' out
...

******* This Lyrics is NOT for Commercial use *******
